okay so yeah ecovillages the
permaculture are very important because
it's very easy just to read books about
a green way of life or a deep ecological
way of life and reading books is very
important because you have to nourish
the intellect but ultimately the only
way to learn about what this is really
all about is through experience you have
to actually experience what it's like to
live in community in in a set of organic
buildings with other people or to grow
food in a permaculture issue sort of way
once you've experienced that then what
you read in the books suddenly fall into
place so there's a deeper learning that
happens experientially which can be
provided by an eco village or by a
permaculture project that you can't
simply get through intellectual learning
I think wilderness experience is also
incredibly important probably the most
important thing of all is to experience
what what wilderness is because the
wilderness is where we came from and
what nourishes arts now and what makes
an eco village and permaculture possible
without a matrix of wilderness then we
can't have a guy in configuration that
can favor our existence so the point is
experiential learning is very very
important and I think the eco villages
can really facilitate that and really
make that happen